powerlinkworld.com 2012-07-07

# PowerLink Group

PowerLink is committed to protecting your privacy on the Internet. We believe that it is important for you to know what we do with your personal information.   
Should you choose to respond directly to PowerLink with comments, questions, suggestions, ideas or the like relating to this Web Site or PowerLink products and services, you agree that such information shall be deemed as non-confidential and PowerLink shall have no obligation to respond and be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute the information to others without limitation, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products incorporating such information. 

When we collect domain names, this information may be aggregated on a "no name" basis just to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, or page s viewed. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive, which allows the server to recognize the computer when it visits again. This helps track statistical information about navigation through our site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation. PowerLink uses these data to measure the usage of, and improve the content of our sites.

**Others**  
In an effort to make your visit both efficient and safe, all transfers of personal information via this site meet Internet security standards.  
Occasionally, our site may contain electronic links to other sites. In case you choose to go to those sites, their own privacy policy and privacy preferences will apply.  
If you feel that the PowerLink Web site (http://www.Powerlinkworld.com) is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, Please contact.

Products

PowerLink air compressors (screw air compressors) mainly include: soundproof fixed sets, soundproof diesel-driven fixed sets .... 

News

2011-6-23 

## Site Observation and Validation Meeting [...] 

On the afternoon of June 22, site observation and validation meeting of stock products hel [...] 

2011-6-20 

## Open Market, Elegant Appearance - WPS350 [...] 

On June 13, 2011, the 14th Chile International Mining Equipment Exhibition EXPONOR held gr [...] 

2011-6-11 

## Thailand Customers Delegation Visited Po [...] 

On June 10, 20 people of a business delegation consisted of PowerLink’s exclusive dealer i [...]
